<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-04-12T10:27:39-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Shogo Toyonaga</title><subtitle>A blog about technology and stuff related</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Social Networks - The Tracking of COVID-19 Misinformation Using NLP and Graph-based Approaches</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Social-Networks-The-Tracking-of-COVID-19-Misinformation-Using-NLP-and-Graph-based-Approaches/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Social Networks - The Tracking of COVID-19 Misinformation Using NLP and Graph-based Approaches" /><published>2024-04-09T10:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-04-09T10:16:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Social%20Networks%20-%20The%20Tracking%20of%20COVID-19%20Misinformation%20Using%20NLP%20and%20Graph-based%20Approaches</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Social-Networks-The-Tracking-of-COVID-19-Misinformation-Using-NLP-and-Graph-based-Approaches/">&lt;h1&gt;Social Networks: The Tracking of COVID-19 Misinformation Using NLP and Graph-based Approaches&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Introduction:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Misinformation during the COVID-19 pandemic resulted in many unnecessary infections, hospitalizations, and fatalities [10]. This is a trend that has been seen in past health epidemics [11, 12]. Our work aims to study the spread of COVID-19 misinformation on social media platforms such as Twitter and Reddit through a Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Graph-based approach. We use NetworkX, Gephi, Streamlit, Plotly, and Large Language Models to build a comprehensive analytics and visualization system that that is capable of extracting core metrics identifying malicious users in the social network. Lastly, our results are consistent with previous work [1], however, we extend on what has been done by contributing a robust QA Dashboard system that is interactive and intuitive for users to learn about vaccine misinformation. This work can be valuable for many organizations that aim to address misinformation as it provides an actionable framework to implement.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/4160059/pexels-photo-4160059.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=2&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Technical Details&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Analytics:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;NetworkX, Gephi, NTLK, re, and PowerLaw&lt;/em&gt; were use to build our graphs and analyze its properties.&lt;/li&gt;
         &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Augmentation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Transformers&lt;/em&gt; were used to augment the initial dataset with columns relating to sentiment score (negative, neutral, positive) and information validity. We also used PRAW to collect Reddit posts and comments to augment our initial datasets and provide a more comprehensive analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Visualization:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly, Wordcloud, Streamlit&lt;/em&gt; were used to visualize the graph and NLP-related properties of our datasets.&lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ol&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Source Code &amp;amp; Paper&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;All of our code, datasets, gexf files, and more can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stoyonaga/EECS6414_SocialNetworks/tree/main&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;To obtain the written paper, please reach out to me!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>shogz</name></author><category term="project" /><category term="Data Analytics &amp; Visualization" /><summary type="html">Social Networks: The Tracking of COVID-19 Misinformation Using NLP and Graph-based Approaches Introduction: Misinformation during the COVID-19 pandemic resulted in many unnecessary infections, hospitalizations, and fatalities [10]. This is a trend that has been seen in past health epidemics [11, 12]. Our work aims to study the spread of COVID-19 misinformation on social media platforms such as Twitter and Reddit through a Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Graph-based approach. We use NetworkX, Gephi, Streamlit, Plotly, and Large Language Models to build a comprehensive analytics and visualization system that that is capable of extracting core metrics identifying malicious users in the social network. Lastly, our results are consistent with previous work [1], however, we extend on what has been done by contributing a robust QA Dashboard system that is interactive and intuitive for users to learn about vaccine misinformation. This work can be valuable for many organizations that aim to address misinformation as it provides an actionable framework to implement. Technical Details Data Analytics: NetworkX, Gephi, NTLK, re, and PowerLaw were use to build our graphs and analyze its properties. Data Augmentation:Transformers were used to augment the initial dataset with columns relating to sentiment score (negative, neutral, positive) and information validity. We also used PRAW to collect Reddit posts and comments to augment our initial datasets and provide a more comprehensive analysis. Data Visualization: Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly, Wordcloud, Streamlit were used to visualize the graph and NLP-related properties of our datasets. Source Code &amp;amp; Paper All of our code, datasets, gexf files, and more can be found here. To obtain the written paper, please reach out to me!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">PostgreSQL: Generated Tuning Hints with Large-Language Models by Exploiting NLP</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PostgreSQL/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PostgreSQL: Generated Tuning Hints with Large-Language Models by Exploiting NLP" /><published>2023-12-14T14:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-12-14T14:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PostgreSQL</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PostgreSQL/">&lt;h1&gt;Generated Tuning Hints with Large-Language Models by Exploiting NLP&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Introduction:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Two machine learning models were developed in an effort to reduce the cognitive load on Database Administrators when fine-tuning a PostgreSQL database system. The first model answers simple questions by utilizing embeddings on a custom-tailored knowledge-base consisting of user manuals, YouTube transcripts, and Reddit/Quora posts. The second model uses a Generative Pre-trained Transformer 2 (GPT-2) model with 124M parameters to answer more complex queries that require understanding of semantic relationships and dependencies between parameter non-independence. The training data to fine-tune the model was generated by ChatGPT-4 and the author by leveraging the first models input-output pairs.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/5203849/pexels-photo-5203849.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Technical Details&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model 1: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HayStacks&lt;/em&gt; was used to configure the question-answer pipeline that leveraged sentence-similarity tasks and data preparation/preprocessing from a user-defined knowledge-base.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model 2: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SFTTrainer&lt;/em&gt; was used to fine-tune the GPT2 model on relevant question-answer pairs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Scraping: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;PlayWright, BeautifulSoup4&lt;/em&gt; were used to webscrape tuning-hints from Reddit/Quora and save them into the user-defined knowledge-base as text files. Additionally, &lt;em&gt;youtube-transcript-api&lt;/em&gt; was used to obtain text files that contained transcripts from conferences that discussed tuning-related hints.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Tools: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ChatGPT4&lt;/em&gt; was used to help generate training data to finetune the LLM.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Source Code &amp;amp; Paper&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;The source code was developed on Google Colab. You can access the notebook and dataset &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stoyonaga/EECS6415_LLMs&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;To access additional files (i.e., written report), please feel free to reach out to me!! :)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>shogz</name></author><category term="project" /><category term="Machine Learning" /><summary type="html">Generated Tuning Hints with Large-Language Models by Exploiting NLP Introduction: Two machine learning models were developed in an effort to reduce the cognitive load on Database Administrators when fine-tuning a PostgreSQL database system. The first model answers simple questions by utilizing embeddings on a custom-tailored knowledge-base consisting of user manuals, YouTube transcripts, and Reddit/Quora posts. The second model uses a Generative Pre-trained Transformer 2 (GPT-2) model with 124M parameters to answer more complex queries that require understanding of semantic relationships and dependencies between parameter non-independence. The training data to fine-tune the model was generated by ChatGPT-4 and the author by leveraging the first models input-output pairs. Technical Details Model 1: HayStacks was used to configure the question-answer pipeline that leveraged sentence-similarity tasks and data preparation/preprocessing from a user-defined knowledge-base. Model 2: SFTTrainer was used to fine-tune the GPT2 model on relevant question-answer pairs. Web Scraping: PlayWright, BeautifulSoup4 were used to webscrape tuning-hints from Reddit/Quora and save them into the user-defined knowledge-base as text files. Additionally, youtube-transcript-api was used to obtain text files that contained transcripts from conferences that discussed tuning-related hints. External Tools: ChatGPT4 was used to help generate training data to finetune the LLM. Source Code &amp;amp; Paper The source code was developed on Google Colab. You can access the notebook and dataset here. To access additional files (i.e., written report), please feel free to reach out to me!! :)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sentiment Analysis: WellnessOracle</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/WellnessOracle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sentiment Analysis: WellnessOracle" /><published>2023-12-14T12:41:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-12-14T12:41:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/WellnessOracle</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/WellnessOracle/">&lt;h1&gt;WellnessOracle: A Machine Learning Approach to Suicide Ideation Classification&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;WellnessOracle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a text-based binary classifier that aims to predict a social media user's mental well-being based on their previous posting and/or comment history. It aims to determine signs of underlying depression so that the machine learning model can quickly determine if a user is mentally at-risk to themselves or others. Suicide, especially for the younger generation, has become an increasingly pervasive problem [8]. It has become the second-most leading cause of fatality [5] among young adults worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/5598393/pexels-photo-5598393.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Technical Details&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;sklearn, seaborn, GridSearchCV&lt;/em&gt; were use to develop and fine-tune the model for text-based classification tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Visualization:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;matplotlib, seaborn, wordcloud&lt;/em&gt; were used to visualize model performance on the training and testing set and to identify patterns between keywords.&lt;/li&gt; 
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Scraping:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;PlayWright, BeautifulSoup4, Requests&lt;/em&gt; were used to webscrape content from Reddit, Twitter, and Quora to further evaluate the model's performance on real-time data.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Graphical User Interface (GUI):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Streamlit&lt;/em&gt; was used to support the end-user with an intuitive user interface that interacts with our pre-trained models. Data from various websites can be scraped and automatically classified as suicide or non-suicide.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Source Code &amp;amp; Paper&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;The training and testing data used to generate our models can be accessed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/nikhileswarkomati/suicide-watch&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Our code can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stoyonaga/EECS5327_WellnessOracle&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>shogz</name></author><category term="project" /><category term="Machine Learning" /><summary type="html">WellnessOracle: A Machine Learning Approach to Suicide Ideation Classification WellnessOracle is a text-based binary classifier that aims to predict a social media user's mental well-being based on their previous posting and/or comment history. It aims to determine signs of underlying depression so that the machine learning model can quickly determine if a user is mentally at-risk to themselves or others. Suicide, especially for the younger generation, has become an increasingly pervasive problem [8]. It has become the second-most leading cause of fatality [5] among young adults worldwide. Technical Details Machine Learning: sklearn, seaborn, GridSearchCV were use to develop and fine-tune the model for text-based classification tasks. Data Visualization: matplotlib, seaborn, wordcloud were used to visualize model performance on the training and testing set and to identify patterns between keywords. Web Scraping: PlayWright, BeautifulSoup4, Requests were used to webscrape content from Reddit, Twitter, and Quora to further evaluate the model's performance on real-time data. Graphical User Interface (GUI): Streamlit was used to support the end-user with an intuitive user interface that interacts with our pre-trained models. Data from various websites can be scraped and automatically classified as suicide or non-suicide. Source Code &amp;amp; Paper The training and testing data used to generate our models can be accessed here. Our code can be found here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Course Note-Taking</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Notes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Course Note-Taking" /><published>2023-12-14T07:31:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-12-14T07:31:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Notes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Notes/">&lt;h1&gt;Note Taking @ York&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;EECS-Notes GitHub Repository&lt;/strong&gt; is a project that I started working on during the Winter 2023 semester. Originally, it was mostly used to share my programming solutions with the instructor of a fourth year cryptography course. Overtime, it has become a repository in which I share my midterm and/or exam review notes for challenging upper-year programming courses such as Operating Systems, Algorithms &amp;amp; Analysis, Database Systems, Human-Computer Interaction, and Machine Learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like to share tutoring resources in order to facilitate growth in others. By doing so, and making such materials more accessible, it is my hope that students feeling overwhelmed by certain concepts can truly come to learn and enjoy the material. Lastly, it is my hope that by doing so, it inspires others to join an open-source movement in which they share their work with others to benefit the greatest amount of people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Course Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is a non-exhaustive list. To view a sample version of the notes, please visit the corresponding GitHub repository.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Machine Learning --&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning &amp;amp; Pattern Recognition (GS/EECS 5327): &lt;/strong&gt;Machine learning is the study of algorithms that learn how to perform a task from prior experience. This course introduces the student to machine learning concepts and techniques applied to pattern recognition problems in a diversity of application areas. &lt;strong&gt;Sample notes can be obtained &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.overleaf.com/project/656694966fe5cad0eae543a6&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/17485706/pexels-photo-17485706/free-photo-of-an-artist-s-illustration-of-artificial-intelligence-ai-this-image-visualises-the-input-and-output-of-neural-networks-and-how-ai-systems-perceive-data-it-was-created-by-rose-pilkington.png?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- Human-Computer Interaction --&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/256262/pexels-photo-256262.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Human-Computer Interaction (LE/EECS 4441): &lt;/strong&gt; Introduces the concepts and technology necessary to design, manage and implement interactive software. Students work in small groups and learn how to design user interfaces, how to realize them and how to evaluate the end result. Both design and evaluation are emphasized. &lt;strong&gt;Sample notes can be obtained &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stoyonaga/EECS-Notes/tree/main/EECS%204441&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- Operating Systems --&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating System Fundamentals (LE/EECS 3221): &lt;/strong&gt;Principles of operating systems. Concurrent processes, CPU scheduling, deadlocks, memory management, file systems, protection and security, and case studies. &lt;strong&gt;Sample notes can be obtained &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stoyonaga/EECS-Notes/tree/main/EECS%203221&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/2582928/pexels-photo-2582928.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- Mathematics of Cryptography --&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;side-by-side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;toleft&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://images.pexels.com/photos/7319085/pexels-photo-7319085.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;toright&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mathematics of Cryptography (LE/EECS 4161): &lt;/strong&gt;Probability, information theory and number theory and applications to cryptography. Classical codes such as Caesar shift, Vigenere, ADFGVX, rectangular substitution, and others. Other topics: comma free codes, perfect secrecy, index of coincidence, public key systems, primality testing and factorization algorithms. &lt;strong&gt;Sample notes can be obtained &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/stoyonaga/Cryptography&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>shogz</name></author><category term="project" /><category term="LaTeX" /><summary type="html">Note Taking @ York Introduction The EECS-Notes GitHub Repository is a project that I started working on during the Winter 2023 semester. Originally, it was mostly used to share my programming solutions with the instructor of a fourth year cryptography course. Overtime, it has become a repository in which I share my midterm and/or exam review notes for challenging upper-year programming courses such as Operating Systems, Algorithms &amp;amp; Analysis, Database Systems, Human-Computer Interaction, and Machine Learning. Motivation I like to share tutoring resources in order to facilitate growth in others. By doing so, and making such materials more accessible, it is my hope that students feeling overwhelmed by certain concepts can truly come to learn and enjoy the material. Lastly, it is my hope that by doing so, it inspires others to join an open-source movement in which they share their work with others to benefit the greatest amount of people. Course Notes The following is a non-exhaustive list. To view a sample version of the notes, please visit the corresponding GitHub repository. Machine Learning &amp;amp; Pattern Recognition (GS/EECS 5327): Machine learning is the study of algorithms that learn how to perform a task from prior experience. This course introduces the student to machine learning concepts and techniques applied to pattern recognition problems in a diversity of application areas. Sample notes can be obtained here. Human-Computer Interaction (LE/EECS 4441): Introduces the concepts and technology necessary to design, manage and implement interactive software. Students work in small groups and learn how to design user interfaces, how to realize them and how to evaluate the end result. Both design and evaluation are emphasized. Sample notes can be obtained here. Operating System Fundamentals (LE/EECS 3221): Principles of operating systems. Concurrent processes, CPU scheduling, deadlocks, memory management, file systems, protection and security, and case studies. Sample notes can be obtained here. Mathematics of Cryptography (LE/EECS 4161): Probability, information theory and number theory and applications to cryptography. Classical codes such as Caesar shift, Vigenere, ADFGVX, rectangular substitution, and others. Other topics: comma free codes, perfect secrecy, index of coincidence, public key systems, primality testing and factorization algorithms. Sample notes can be obtained here.</summary></entry></feed>